First, here's how I went about creating a vocab
先说说如何创建 vocab_to_int 字典
to int dictionary and encoding our word data,
并对字词数据进行编码
and there are a few ways to do this.
实现方式有多种
I chose to use this important counter to create a dictionary that
我使用这个导入的 Counter 创建一个字典
maps the most common words in our reviews text to the smallest integers.
它会将影评文本中的最常见字词映射到最小的整数
So the first thing I'm doing is to get a count of how many times each of our words
首先调用 Counter 并传入 words
actually appears in our data using counter and passing in our words.
对每个字词在数据中的出现次数进行计数
Then with these counts, I'm creating assorted vocabulary.
获得这些计数后 创建一个有序词汇表
This sorts each unique word by its frequency of occurrence.
根据每个唯一字词的出现频率排序
So this vocab should hold all of the unique words that
这个 vocab 包含了数据中的所有唯一字词
make up our word data without any repeats,
没有任何重复字词
and it will be sorted by commonality.
并且按出现频率排序
I also know that I want to start encoding
在用整数值编码字词时
my words with the integer value of one rather than zero.
我们需要从 1（而不是 0）开始
So the most common word like be or of should actually be encoded as one.
所以“the”或“of”等最常见的字词应该编码为 1
I'm making sure that we start our indexing at one by using
在这里使用枚举并传入 vocab 和起始索引 1
enumerate and passing in our vocab and our starting index, one.
这样就能使索引从 1 开始
Enumerate is going to return a numerical value,
enumerate 将返回一个数字值 ii
ii, and a word in our vocabulary. It will do this in order.
以及词汇表中的一个字词enumerate 会按顺序返回
So our first index is going to be one,
所以第一个索引是 1
and the first word is going to be the most common word in our assorted vocabulary.
第一个字词将是有序词汇表中的最常见字词
So to create the dictionary vocab to int,
要创建 vocab_to_int 字典
I'm taking each unique word in our vocab and
需要获取 vocab 中的每个唯一字词
mapping it to an index starting at the value one.
并将它映射到从 1 开始的索引
Great. Next, I'm using this dictionary to tokenize all of our word data.
很棒接下来使用该字典标记化所有字词数据
So here, I'm looking at each individual review.
在这里查看每条影评
Each of these is one item and review split
每个影评都是 review_split 中的一个条目
from before when I separated reviews by the newline character.
我之前用换行符拆分影评时创建了这个 review_split
Then, for each word in a review,
对于影评中的每个字词
I'm using my dictionary to convert that word into its integer value,
我都使用字典将该字词转换为整数值
and I'm appending the token as review to reviews_ints.
并将标记化的影评附加到 reviews_ints 上
So the end result will be a list of tokenized reviews.
最终结果是一个标记化影评列表
Here in the cells below, I'm printing out
我在单元格下面
the length of my dictionary and my first sample encoded review.
输出了字典长度和第一个示例标记化影评
I can see that my dictionary is a bit over 74,000 words long,
字典长度为 74,000 多个字词
which means that we have this many unique words that make up our reviews data.
也就是说 影评数据有 74,000 多个唯一字词
Let's take a look at this tokenized review.
我们来看看这条标记化影评
I'm not seeing any zero values which is good,
里面没有任何 0，不错
and these encoded values look as I might expect.
这些编码值符合预期
So I've successfully encoded the review words,
成功编码影评字词后
and I'll move on to the next task,
下一步是
which is encoding our labels.
对标签进行编码
So in this case, I want to look at
我们需要查看标签文本数据
my label's text data and turn the word positive into one and negative into zero.
并将“positive”转换成 1 将“negative”转换成 0
Now we haven't much processed our labels data,
我们还没有预处理标签数据
and I know much like the reviews text that a new label is on every new line in this file.
不过每个标签都各占一行 与影评文本很像
So I can get a list of labels, labels_split,
可以用换行符作为分隔符
by splitting our loaded in data using the newline character as a delimiter.
将加载的数据拆分成单个标签 并获得 labels_split 列表
Then I just have a statement that says,
然后使用一个 for 语句
for every label in this label_split list,
对于 label_split 列表中的每个标签
I'm going to add one to my array if it reads as positive,
如果内容为“positive” 则向数组中添加 1
and a zero otherwise.
否则向数组中添加 0
I'm wrapping this in np.array,
将这行代码放入 np.array 中
and that's all I need to do to create an array of encoded labels. All right.
这样就能创建 encoded_labels 数组了好的
This is a good start. There are still a few data clean up and
数据处理得差不多了不过在定义模型之前
formatting steps that I'll want to take before we get to defining our model.
还有几个数据清理和格式设定步骤
So let's address those tasks next.
下面我们就来完成这些步骤吧